Hello hello everyone welcome back to home channels
playing friends in today's first video
I have the mid market let's discuss all the important
news and indicators
as I saw in all the indicators and updates in this video
and also in the market meanwhile there is
not much quality in the mid difficult
indicators quite good technical indicators the
lid of the pan is rocking the previous generation and again doing
four inches on some of its long term trend slabs
so this quality may remain for the next few
days so we
feel that this is the time to take a come to speak approach
and keep replying to your investments on the road keeping
all these news in
mind which
fundamentals can you
add current color for some office meetings which are
available to you at good valuations and
which press clubs can you buy them, I will
discuss that in this video friends if
you haven't subscribed to my channel then do it
now and press the bell icon
because we keep doing like this on a weekly basis best
of two bank watch live  We keep updating the score
and keep sharing it with you,
which can be very difficult for you,
so without advertisements,
hello friends, even at this time, the same stocks that we are discussing for the staff
personnel,
they did it for the previous time also because many of the
stocks from me, almost all the stocks which are
still department and person market and
back, still all these stocks are available at good price levels for all the staff,
many of these stocks are at
better prices than the previous price level,
just you should definitely not lose sight
of the
difficulties of very very fundamentalism
staff and dear, all available at discounted
and and novel and good consolidation support
levels midcap unknown all these talks due to which
I have again inputted all these staff here,
so Laddu Tower Discussion
friends, today's description of our first
company Britannia Adams, in this we are talking about
a giant company Britannia
Industries in India and
before starting all the distractions, let me
remind you once  That is
not a video in which they will do a dipper number of channels of all the staff,
here they will take all the stock
tips 13 and their price Awasthi will
talk for space, but there is a different
board for it, a
flexible playlist has been made for soft
metals in which HDFC Bank, ITC
Limited has already done a different ambulance,
they have watched the videos, you will see
how we will
analyze and understand all these staff one by one, we will
understand them and all the
fundamental parameters of the whole business, but we are
not going to do that in this video, this video is a
review, there is an increase in
which we take 20 overs from the price opportunity company,
but for the playlist of that fundamental address,
here is the donut,
from there you can also take a beauty over,
how we will do detailed research of all these companies, by
doing that, so come back to the
discussion of today's video, our
first company, as you said, Britannia
Industries, is a big company,
its marks have been around 84 thousand crores, the
comments are also quite turmeric, a
blurred turmeric of one person  The
beta tester points will be considered 142. For the
viewers who are watching our videos for the first time, please
revise them once. There is a beta
tester which tells that the
particular topic is less than the overall market
or more quality. If
Jaipur is less than number one, then we assume that
that particular stock is less than the overall market and
Britain and now it is more than number one,
then we assume that it will get more votes on TikTok than the overall market. Those who
only watch the music of Egg Bhurji company, they also watch every
clear view, then in this they do
more than you, that Pharma, IT, FMCG,
all these apps, chapters, then there are
conservatives, actors, defense
sector, 71, their beta is less than 1. If
we are seeing vitamin A specific
company from us here, then its beta points are
less than 141, then less than the market. On let's talk about the
industry's base sperm of 7172,
you are getting a very good discount,
almost 1850, so like
definitely trading at a  Discount Fanda
Industries You can definitely start admission in it at the pay level and top current level.
We are going to talk about at which level
you want to start accommodation on this occasion
or keep it continued. If such measures are
discussed at the level, we will talk about the conservative level, we are going to
talk about removing all leaves immediately.
Now you can see 50% 12%. This shows
that people have started taking delivery of their long-term
investments. 3D
Women in long-term interest. In these texts, let's talk about the
good level. Now let's talk about
12%, its delivery percentage which is around 25-30 percent is
considered quite turmeric.
This very very healthy robust delivery
percentage. I have to subscribe to Electric Britannia
Industries for 1 minute. 34735,
which is around the current price. So, at
this level you can start the list in your eyes.
Now you can see that many times the
staff has taken this decision on this bundle, so
it is definitely a good support level for
tackling vitamins, but if you want to wait a little then
3000 to 310 price
level can be updated there if
you all see this company but I do
n't have much conference on it,
it will come again on this channel but if you
want to do Savita wait on it, then
go to this level tech
medicine and you can start in 1 minute
but even under current price
lovers note price service tax meeting
attend speed our next company is also a
digital platform c company hu is
HAL's market capitalization is very
big you used to see how many big
companies have a scheme market capitalization of 5 lakh 5.5 lakh crores
Daniel is
quite healthy around one and a half percent
and you will have contacted so it was
less than vitamins but both are
NCC companies and this is a
low voltage stock than Britain, it is on the order of the overall market,
so a very low voltage stock is
getting around the base MP4 of the industry or around the price of some similar industry on the back of 7273 and
you can see the delivery percentage here also very
high help delivery percentage go and  Very
strong delivery percentage shift
delivery percentage of this form will become
I think at this pace 2250 can only
bring a good offer if you
want to start admissions in April then this
thank you very strong price level you
can see that sir good support levels for
regulating actual but if you
want to wait a little more now conservative and
resturant want to wait a little
according to your taste then you can wait from 2000 to 21 a capital
there the level
of steel in Bijnor Shetty will increase further
problems in the last step meeting natural
problem then our next company is
pharmaceutical company this friends let's
talk about multinational pharmaceutical company Sanofi India is a French company
its Indian subsidiaries of India we are
talking about its market in it
ribbon is around 18,000 crore it is a midcap
companies difficult office fantastic and Moses has
blurred 4% and along with that it
also gives you capital appreciation money training long  In terms of both,
if you look at both, this
is a great company. Whenever you want to
invest from a different perspective, this can be a very
strong candidate for you. But if you want to invest, it is a much lower-
volume stock than the market. Its computer market is at a very low level. Its
base is 38th in the overall industry, and you are
getting a payment of around 3940 at the same yellow level. The
computer industry average speed is
higher. The delivery
percentage is quite strong. This shows that people have started investing in it for a long time. This
priceless gem. Subscribe to 7528 subscribers starting from page number 90.
So, subscribe to this channel. You should
wait a little
and subscribe. Due to the overall quality in the market,
if you subscribe, you can
increase your subscription by 1000 times.
So, subscribe to our next company,
India's largest company
in the industry. If we talk about very
big companies, then they have a
company in points
system, so it will be considered a bag.  These
growth companies do
n't do much different, but you're seeing a slightly lower rate of this at the
B-test point, so it's
much lower than the market. The
industry's pay is clear. 1922 is quite high.
This industry's staff rates are
quite high behind the industry. 193, and
you're seeing this at a slightly higher
valuation. So, these are fundamentally
sound companies and multi-
brands. The largest wealth creators in 25
minutes. Every student. So, it's natural for such companies to
get some creamy pay. So,
look here, a
slightly different version of the industry's position. You're seeing a
delivery percentage of 80%. Answer, the
delivery percentage is definitely a little low.
So, you can take this approach at the spice level. You
can convert Asian Paints to this decision. Let's talk about it. 25
and 26 levels. I think that 25 and 26 levels can be a
good initial
starting point for a good examination if you
want to invest in stocks.  And
I think that about which
Rock Play Store in Western India, if
you want to invest in it, then 2526
is the only country where you can
start accommodation in the
field of your investments, you can make a
statement to me and if you get this stock at the
level of 22 so strongly, if
such a body comes in the market, if some such
good correction comes, then 21-22 and colour can get
even better price, its
support level is there also and you can
cancel the investment there, so
both our labels message in this also, more
computer plot like your conviction
revolution printer closed Sanjay, you
can only invest in these West Indies,
which decision will
suit you more, the leading company of our discussion
is About India, this pharmaceutical
company is a multinational company, now it is a tax
less accuracy company, we are talking about such Indian
subsidiary All India,
its market capitalization is around 13238 crore,
dual is quite good  This is quite turmeric
daily point seven four percent beta 12th
much lower than the market bone test office
elected
1520 seal it is nutritious to you
in a little print at metro station it
is not a very overvalued stock it does not have very high
expenses top if you are
interested compare telephone number
tele quite strong companies industry
overall industry of this chapter complete
but you are not getting a little prem western
very much tube edition
habit current price level 6 per cent very
excellent very strong delivery was presented
so this shows that a lot of people are taking delivery of long term insurance in their
investment account not in trading account but
in investment account Javeri
turmeric science I think that to invest in About India the
current price is 14000 and a half 14020 in fact it is very close
you can already start investing there
we also did a little
investment in this on our telegram channel
we sent a notification that if you
want to do Airport India win 10 then
forcibly promising  Labels to staff meeting
about India and investment take off but if you
want to wait a little then 13 6073 level
and more promises
can come to you, your level of safety
Amazon objective will increase a little more and
there you can start investments for long term
examination. Madrid,
Spain's leading company Nestle, Nestle
India's Indian subsidiary Ambedkar,
its market place in India is one of the
largest state functions company schedule, along with
its market complex of Rs 1
lakh 70 thousand crore, it is a very big company,
David is quite excellent,
almost 2% of 1.94 percent, and growth companies
with it, such a good agreement, you have it that the
number on this, how sound company is, is
3.5 inches, so much less than the market,
say, type of industries panic
around the disagreement of a beautiful girl and it will
pay you active 182, so there are some expenses, it is a
computer industry, but the
company is much stronger than Intercity Express,
so its specifications are a little bit
Prevention justified that there was a
delivery percentage of 35 percent. The increase in the
t-shirt pimpl delivery percentage shows
that people have started dominating the Spice Channel.
I think the
latest current price of 17,000-68,000 is
quite close to it. You
can start its entry there if you are
not already interested in it, then
if you want to wait a little, then
15016 and a half is a good support level of Ajay Lovely,
there you can make its accommodation and if he
beats it, the next
companies in our discussion were present in Muthoot Finance Gold Final, one of the
largest companies in India, it is a
very strong and waves free fruit,
its market capitalization is around 40-48
crores, dividend will be quite good.
Turmeric is different or around 1.3 percent,
tasty 1.2 percent. Now we have
seen in many videos before that the
stock of Bhains BSC Final Factor has a
bit high beta, whereas you are seeing a
bit more orders than the market.  There are
other tiles, but you will
always see that the
beta of financial sector stocks is more than 1. That is, for reference, easy for them. If
you look at the stocks of the IT sector, then
their beta is less than 1. So,
earlier also, you talked about Jaisalmer district, and
their
beta was less than 1. But Muthoot Finance,
because it is a stock of any sector, its beta
is more than the industry's fifty
and you are getting it at a huge discount.
Now you can see that the industry base is
around Nifty, you are getting it at a very important
thing like protein. So
definitely, trading and discount
completed industry average is
36 per cent and differently-abled delivery
percentage, which shows that people have
also started with Laxman Singh Sperm.
I think to invest in Muthoot Finance, you
can ask from Chapra of 1112 for starting. Now you can
see that many times Stark has
taken support at this price level, so please
Definitely good love, to stock meeting
is over etc. want to wait a bit if
you feel that there can be a little correction in the stock,
disaster free number of two, level of 9.50 to
1000, good pressure can increase,
then reach from the tractor price, if that
preserve profit is obtained, then this was the
Infinity stock meeting in the same manner at a
price level, my discussion, Yagya company
Adidas, the
only quiz maker in India, in a
global level, one of the largest
manufacturer appears in the world, entire
world class almost 67 percent through all
the pain killer appears in the world, which
lottery makes syrup on that side, fifty
percent of all global manufacturing of a
piece of it only makes, so in this topic
description, in more detail, best
of Indore pharma sector medicine was discussed,
those stocks for investment in pharma
sector, in that, its details of this question were done by
capturing that video and you can't get a little idea
that why Bigg Boss notices
me so much, then this company  The
market place has around 95 thousand 944
roads, depending on the daily point, sewerage has
passed 11.57, so less than the market, let's
talk, it is
available at a little valuation of the industry's authority notification,
but the delivery is so good, you
can see that there is a delivery percentage of 22%,
it shows that people should start taking delivery of it in
long-term withdrawals in their investment accounts, the level of
looter 3435 can be a very good
starting point, fundamental link office,
which company is FD, good marks, travel
companies, its function researchers, so
you will not have to spend much time for such a strong company,
but still I
think that you can see that it had
reached burst or waste in 3839 square, from there after a
good addition correction,
after good consolidation, then
34 and 35 are available at good price channel around the fourth level, you
can start investing
in divisional water, but if you
want to wait a little, from 3000  31 Stock
Price Travels Paper Admission can start in
these we are further ahead but the next company
Amar Distraction Refinery and K Nitya
Specialty Chemical Companies are small
companies, small cap companies but
fundamentally very sound companies, its
products are very nice, it
makes a lot of sprinters to the market but
fundamentally very good companies,
we have discussed it in the Talks for Investment
in Chemical Sector video,
in that video we can see the discussion of the office in a better
way
that the market capitalization of storms and scissors is
around 7.5 thousand crores,
definitely it is a competitive company, daily point
to line, so since small car companies are
investing money in their group, it is
not dependent on much right now, hence its
deal is a little less, but as the company forces,
grows, stratifies its
market share, so its delivery
may fall, but that is why it is a little less because when the
school is down and the company limited is 3.77, then the
stock trades less than the market, there is
a little premium vibration around the price of the industry,
then it is definitely available, it is available at a
good valuation in the trophy  Yes, but
fundamentally it is a very soft company, so
you will have to look at this cream vibration
holistically,
why prevention is being given to it, and
you can see that 727 percent is a very
strong delivery percentage,
people have started taking delivery of it in large numbers, I will
tell you that its
price level of 2425 is a good price, it has
reduced at that time in waiting for
organic, which we have been discussing in the last two-three process
credits, and since the prices
are consolidated,
you
can definitely stop eating and deserve, but
if you want to wait a little, and Turkey is
a small cap, so if any correction comes in it,
and 1800 which is the price leveler or
1819, definitely do it before this friends, and it
got a very attractive price tag, it is our
leading company of depression, it is a multinational
pharmacist company, very high quality of
pharmaceutical company, Spice f302, its market
capitalization is around 22 crores,
you can see its denial of 70% or for six
Around 7%, so in this period of FD
you get so much comment, perhaps
even in this period you do not get
such a dominant bank in the short term
and that gives you such a strong
dental, this company has taken you and with
capital appreciation price of it is a
very good company office from giving
benefits, the key points data is
much lower than the market, this topic as we have also discussed
pharma stocks, their yield is less, that is what
we are seeing here, the base of the industry is
around 2010, the
team is not getting much interest on the husband,
take the current price and
unmute this 2009 20x interest premium
calculation of 5 percent delivery
percentage of which very strong delivery
percentage for admission, I think
that from 4750 to 4859, a
good price can be seen in the coming years, so
want to start at meeting Pfizer, if
you want this stock around 4041  At pass level, you can get
forces of but reply and can get even more
attractive prices there,
you can start its dominance even more if you invest in
market power
companies like this, it is shallow but in general insurance, one of the
largest private players in
India itself but the most fundamentally sound
company, we are talking about its market
application ISI but it is
also known as general insurance, so
its market capitalization is around 65 thousand crores,
definitely it is a very low growth
company, then its deal is a little less, you are
putting your processor, you must have seen the stocks of pension sector
that their demand is
not very high, we
can see that despite being a sector in the financial sector, its beta
point note is absolutely comparable to the market, on
task channel we see that in the financial sector
also, the beta of the stocks of life insurance sector or
general insurance sector is a
little less, they are a
little less bold style than the market,
we are seeing that here the industry is
speedy, so you will get some prevent 34
on the back  It is happening but the
delivery percentage on Chhitu is almost 1-2%, this
shows that people have done the second edition
and list it, I think that
regarding 1314 and a half, the staff of such a person in Chapra will have a
meeting, such numbers will be seen now, it had
reached the level of sixteen and a half, sixteen hundred and fifty,
but after a little different correction from there,
you are getting a good consolidation range,
if you also want to wait a little on the current price table
then 121  Up to 3 levels, there is
another attractive price that
can be seen. You can see that the stock has seen
support many times. This festival has seen a rise. Thank you, very
strong price levels and YouTube
Bluetooth settings. Album Bird. Our
next and last companies' description of the depression is
that Gujarat State Petronet
Limited (GSPL) can be
considered a midcap company. The market application of border lines is
around 11060 to 11 thousand
crores. It can be considered a company between small cap and midcap.
Delhi is quite
good. If we take an increase of 1 cent on point nine almost one, then it will be
considered to be significantly diminished. If it is a son of point system, then it has
less bililateral tokes than the market. Gas
distribution, city gas distribution,
CNG, compressed natural gas, CNG
partnerships, it is a
very big company in the distribution and transmission of all these.
Its business in Gujarat is quite good.
You can consider it a monopoly business.
Within that region and that chapter, there is industry P.
It is around 10:30,
around 10.5 and this is the back of the industry.
You are getting those points around 100, so there are a
lot of decently valid companies, there are a lot of
good Bollywood companies, there are not valid companies,
almost 60% to 12%, this shows that
people have started investing in it at a good level,
I think that the pizza bread
between 195 to 205 is very promising for investing in GSPL,
thank you, it had
reached the Pacific almost political level again after repeating and recovering,
but from there again there is Addison correction
and on this occasion it also took support many times,
so I think this
price is definitely a good price,
reduced at admitting to start
investing in JSP, are you taking up, if you
want to wait a little, if you are a little
conservative in restaurant, you should wait a little for the
market correction, then you
can update from 175, there it will move towards through you,
there you can be more
aggressive in minor on this  You can start investing,
but fundamentally these are very good companies.
Partnership Research Officer, Congress company
is of PSU staff, hence it does
not get a very high valuation, but
its fundamental performance is very good,
financial ratios of fans, the business which is
then a very monopoly business, its growth
outlook is good in that process, that is why
I like this stock, its evening is
also good, so
after clicking on all these factors, I feel that
its growth potential can be good in the future,
so if you want to invest in stocks, if
you have this best friend,
then you can start
investing in these 10 top depending on your
comfort level, you may
feel more confident in these two price voice messages,
there you can invest in it,
but I hope that all this discussion
on the missions will be helpful to you and for
about 11-12 minutes, all this
talk in the computer, they all have, that
if you invest and set in all your company
or all the
committing updates  If you want reviews, then please let
me know by writing in the comments so that we will keep
reviewing them in more detail. These
fundamentals, terms of pay, all of these gave you
an idea that it will
help you in creating your investment framework and will prove to be very helpful in keeping
your thought process updated for long term investors. Friends, this
information is such magic, I hope so
friends, how is this grass video, which
is Knowledge Power Screen, this is the mission of this channel,
which is to bring the right knowledge to you.
In the coming videos, we will discuss many interesting topics
and I will keep
bringing user guide, user topics for you.
Similarly, every Vikram, Wiki, market update and my
views, till now I will keep discussing the left situation.
Then definitely subscribe to our
channel. If
you liked today's video content, then
like the video. If you think that this
information can help someone, then
share it with your friends and family members and subscribe to the channel. I will meet
you in the next video and
with a discussion on coffee. Till then, take care, see
you.  were able to hear